Guide to the Yale University Master of Fine Arts Theses In Graphic Design
Yale University Arts Library
- Theses
  - Neither here nor there., 2003; Hampole, Ravi (Box 69)
  - Fluctuating fields., 2003; Lee, Albert M. (Box 69)
  - The Hibrid Zone., 2003; Lee, Anita (Box 69)
  - Data=Information II Evocation., 2003; Lee, Jun Y. (Box 70)
  - The Marvelous., 2003; Luna, Ramon (Box 70)
  - Show invisibles., 2003; Moog, Christine (Box 70)
  - Managing Change., 2003; Oiga, Sharon Salameda (Box 70)
  - DIS I., 2003; Ryu, Juyeon (Box 70)
  - Classic Road Test., 2003; Servaas, Jean (Box 70)
  - Gluekit: Collision of Fragments., 2003; Sleboda, Christopher (Box 70)
  - Text is really happening., 2003; Sloat, Andrew (Box 70)
  - From the inside out., 2003; Vizzacchero, Corinne (Box 70)
  - Border, Surface, Interface., 2003; Wu, Yichun (Box 70)
  - Fold., 2003; Yagi, Chisa (Box 70)
  - Error: Undefined Offending Command., 2004; Bowers, Amanda (Box 70)
  - Take your time., 2004; Caserta, John (Box 70)
  - Physical Paths/Collapsed Distance., 2004; Chandani, Natasha (Box 70)
  - Thinking inside the box., 2004; Gifford, Sarah (Box 75)
  - Intruding on the expected., 2004; Janusiak, Brian (Box 70)
  - Do-it-yourself., 2004; Jenkins, Tracy (Box 71)
  - Ephemera Intent., 2004; Kim, Insohngii (Box 71)
  - Terms and conditions., 2004; Lai, Jeffrey (Box 71)
  - Repeat after me., 2004; Lee, Katherine Nahyoung (Box 71)
  - Reading repetition., 2004; Lew, Min Kyong (Box 71)
  - Surface., 2004; Lin, Jammie (Box 71)
  - Mud(tm)corporation., 2004; Okamoto, Takashi (Box 71)
  - Import/Export., 2004; Schmidt, Christian (Box 65)
  - Masked disclosure / by Jena Sher., 2004; Sher, Jena (Box 71)
  - Reorientation: towards an economy of consideration., 2004; Siegel, Dmitri (Box 71)
  - Jumbo Shrimp: monumentalizing miniature., 2004; Teninbaum, Julie (Box 71)
  - Track Record., 2005; Aubert, Danielle (Box 71)
  - Fack Yeah! Graphic Manifesto., 2005; Chapin, Faun (Box 72)
  - Hard Graft., 2005; Edlefson, Brian (Box 72)
  - Axis Sixa., 2005; Grossman, Elena (Box 72)
  - Deviation through /+narrative. The unexpected., 2005; Jakab, Michael (Box 72)
  - Re/design Journeys of Reincarnation., 2005; Kim, Beom Seok (Box 72)
  - Slant., 2005; Kim, Jamerry (Box 72)
  - Documentary Fictions 2002-2005., Liang, Syau-Jyun (Box 72)
  - Mutation., 2005; Lessard, Emily (Box 72)
  - Order and disorder., 2005; Miranda, Manuel (Box 72)
  - Crossing Identitiy, space, form...., 2005; Oh, Susan (Box 72)
  - Interpretation, estimation, evaluation., 2005; Prescott, Elisabeth Ann (Box 72)
  - On modular ..., 2005; Wachowiak, Dirk (Box 75)
  - Embedding., 2005; Wong, Willy (Box 72)
  - Importing., 2005; Yoo, Yoon Seok (Box 72)
  - Grounded., 2005; Yve, Ludwig (Box 72)
  - On systems., 2006; Cavar, Lana (Box 73)
  - Re(Assembly)., 2006; Choi, Yoonjai (Box 73)
  - Exploded Views., 2006; Chun, Michung (Box 73)
  - Misuse., 2006; Dapot, Ian (Box 73)
  - Multiple Perspecitives., 2006; Dzik, Aliza (Box 73)
  - Fracareta, Dylan, 2006 (Box 73)
  - Deflection., 2006; Greenblatt, Michael (Box 73)
  - Contradict., 2006; Griffiths, Thomas (Box 73)
  - On restrictions., 2006; Han, Geoffrey (Box 73)
  - This and or that., 2006; Ho, LaiTsz (Box 73)
  - Magnifying., 2006; Shim, Elizabeth (Box 73)
  - Simple gesture., 2006; Son, Sung Bae (Box 73)
  - Selling., 2006; Unger, Mark (Box 73)
  - About gaps and fragments., 2006; Yen, Jayme (Box 73)
  - Use your imagination., 2006; Young, Forest (Box 73)
  - Make Pretend, 2007; Adolfsen, Eric (Box 73)
  - 35 Cover 2007., Blondes, Brad (Box 73)
  - Campos, Sebastian (Juan Martinez-Campos), 2007 (Box 74)
  - On trying to focus., 2007; Cho, Julie (Box 74)
  - Skin and skeleton, 2007; Feng, Eric (Box 74)
  - Master pieces., 2007; Gallagher, Michael (Box 74)
  - Take me, i'm yours., 2007; Gimenez, Rebecca (Box 74)
  - Rumors., 2007; Ha, Jiminie (Box 74)
  - Now Now Now Now., 2007; Haedrich, Samantha (Box 74)
  - Making of myth/ myths of making., 2007; Howe, Katherine (Box 75)
  - +- [plus minus]., 2007; Millican, Carter (Box 74)
  - Lose something everyday., 2007; Nevin, Eric (Box 74)
  - Catch and release: loosening the diagram., 2007; Park, Romy (Box 74)
  - I'm feeling so real., 2007; Shurtz, Andrew (Box 74)
  - On translation/ sobre la traduccion., 2007; Tejada, Gabriela (Box 74)
  - Title undefined., 2007; Trostle, Robert (Box 74)
  - Acts of Graphic Design., 2008; Bittiner, Julian (Box 78)
  - This Might Be Satire - Sida a & Side b., 2008; Carlberg, Stina (Box 78)
  - Versions., 2008; Celizna, Tomas (Box 78)
  - 20 Questions., 2008; Harding, Daniel Joseph (Box 78)
  - Visual Language., 2008; Joseph, Dawn (Box 81)
  - City As / City of., 2008; Jung, Jin Yeoul (Box 78)
  - Save!, 2008; Larned, Emily (Box 78)
  - 40., 2008; Liu, Lan Lan (Box 78)
  - Stranger Than Fiction., 2008; Manning, Tom (Box 78)
  - This is for us., 2008; Meier, Ken (Box 78)
  - The Story of a Little Girl and Her Stolen Book., 2008; Oh, Min (Box 78)
  - All Time Is Now., 2008; Powell, Bethany (Box 78)
  - January 17, 2003 / April 2008., Rock, Nicholas (Box 78)
  - Bootstrap., 2008; Smith, Stewart (Box 78)
    Smith did not create a stand-alone project. Instead, he contributed to all of the other thesis projects of his classmates.
  - 44 Things., 2008; Wu, Fan (Box 78)
  - We're in this together., 2008; Yun, David Lloyd (Box 78)
  - Big Girl Big Book., 2008; Zargham, Roxane (Box 82)
  - Child star writes autobiography and other short stories. A thesis by Rachel Berger., 2009; Berger, Rachel (Box 79)
  - You, me, here, now: seeing and subjectivity., 2009; Choi, Yeju (Box 79)
  - False starts, full stops., 2009; Donnelly, Neil (Box 79)
  - Light preservation., 2009; Jamieson, Ian (Box 79)
  - Echo of mimesis., 2009; Joe, Hyounyoul (Box 79)
  - Manual: the manual rethinking inefficient disciplines of efficiency. By E Roon Kang., 2009; Kang, E. Roon (Box 79)
  - Moving between., 2009; Katki, Hilla (Box 79)
  - From a third place on perception and dislocation., 2009; Kelton, Tara (Box 79)
  - Caveat emptor., 2009; Konu, Wolasi (Box 79)
  - Mine the gap., 2009; Muspratt, James (Box 79)
  - Collected and Recollected., 2009; Spinat, Daniella (Box 79)
  - Suratman, Yasser, 2009 (Box 79)
  - cf. &c., 2009; Waller, Ryan (Box 79)
  - Design lexicon / compiled by Mary Voorhees., 2009; Voorhees, Mary (Box 79)
  - Dispersed moments: a recollection: Nazima Ahmad., 2010; Ahmad, Nazima (Box 83)
  - Shifting through lens / [by Ke Cao]., 2010; Cao, Ke (Box 83)
  - The Specious present., 2010; Grey, Laura (Box 83)
  - Forms of correspondence., 2010; Halber, Geoffrey (Box 83)
  - Body of work., 2010; Harden, Lauren (Box 83)
  - Based on a true story., 2010; Harris, Luke; 2 (Box 83)
  - The! Scale! Of! Extravaganza!, 2010; Kim, Ely (Box 85)
  - A to B to K to D., 2010; Koppich, Daniel (Box 83)
  - Into the middle: in Medias Res., 2010; Lam, Caspar (Box 83)
  - [Untitled] / by Melissa Levin, 2010; Levin, Melissa (Box 85)
    Includes 2 items.
  - I feel funny., 2010; O'Connor, Kate (Box 83)
  - Material/Immaterial., 2010; Park, YuJune (Box 83)
  - Hyperactivity: when too much from the Factory is never enough for the Supermarket., 2010; Salvas, Jay (Box 83)
    Includes 12 cards and 1 plastic bag.
  - Take care of freedom: (and truth will take care of itself)., 2010; Sarkozy, Steven (Box 83)
  - Dwight & Whalley., 2010; Wellenstein, Vance; 2 (Box 65)
  - It's a cookbook! / [by Lauren Adolfsen]., 2011; Adolfsen, Lauren (Box 87)
  - Catalogue raissoné has twenty-eight letters., 2011; Astasio-Soriano, Juan (Box 87)
  - Nothing ordinary concerning the semiotics of reality-based importance in: Hello., 2011; Bronk, Keri (Box 87)
  - Four-Letter words / B.E.C., 2011; Critton, Benjamin (Box 87)
  - "Portfolio" / [by Lauren Francescone]., 2011; Francescone, Lauren (Box 87)
  - In partial fulfillment / [by Brendan Griffiths]., 2011; Griffiths, Brendan M. (Box 87)
  - Forces & dynamics / [by Bona Han]., 2011; Han, Bona (Box 87)
  - Writing pictures / [Sara Hartman]., 2011; Hartman, Sara (Box 87)
  - My favorite things / Hank Huang., 2011; Huang, Hank H. (Box 87)
  - The other and the others / [by Zeynab Izadyar]., 2011; Izadyar, Zeynab (Box 87)
  - [Untitled] / [by Zak Jensen]., 2011; Jensen, Zakary (Box 87)
  - A Glitch in sequence / [by Zachary Klauck]., 2011; Klauck, Zachary (Box 87)
  - Ready made to order / [by Michael Mikulec]., 2011; Mikulec, Michael (Box 105)
  - Work flow / [by Mylinh Nguyen]., 2011; Nguyen, Mylinh (Box 87)
  - Much later: graphical representations of memory, distance and change over time., 2011; Nordell, Lindsay (Box 87)
  - KN OC K K NO CK / [by Ji-Eun Rim]., 2011; Rim, Ji-Eun (Box 87)
  - Everything within range / [by Brian Watterson]., 2011; Watterson, Brian (Box 87)
  - Placebo / [by Sally Thurer]., 2011; Thurer, Sally (Box 88)
  - [Book 1/3, book 2/3, and book 3/3]., 2012; Çota, Inva (Box 89)
  - Constructions / Kate DeWitt., 2012; DeWitt, Katharine (Box 89)
  - [Untitled], 2012; Esmaili, Golnaz (Box 90)
  - Thesis mixtape., 2012; Gassel, Harry Pollak (Box 89)
  - ESCAPE PLAN., 2012; Harvey, Maxime (Box 89)
  - Vol.01: 5-N.2-S.105-W.10-E., 2012; Henson, Kristian (Box 89)
  - Four hundred forty five pieces of lightness., 2012; Li, Weiyi (Box 89)
  - Another interpretation of the same ruins., 2012; Lister, Andrew James (Box 89)
  - In between spaces., 2012; Liu, Yen-Wei (Box 89)
  - A compilation., 2012; Mutiti, Nontsikelelo Kudzai (Box 89)
  - Reprinting the social narrative., 2012; Pizarro, Daniel (Box 89)
  - An impressionistic device., 2012; Robles, Aurora (Box 89)
  - [Untitled], 2012; Seo, Heesun (Box 89)
  - Product / by-product., 2012; Seok, Jaewon (Box 89)
  - Applied fantastic anthology., 2012; Waefer, Ryan (Box 89)
  - Visual methodologies of subversion., 2012; Yi, Jeseok (Box 89)
  - Journal A & B / by Ming Bai., 2013; Bai, Ming (Box 92)
  - I never learned to write / by Alex Cerrilla., 2013; Cerrilla, Xavier Alejandro (Box 92)
    Includes 16 items total.
  - Draft of a diagram for a satellite / by Matthew Chrislip., 2013; Chrislip, Matthew (Box 92)
  - Stratigraphy / by Njoki Gitahi., 2013; Gitahi, Njoki (Box 92)
  - Unrestrained restriction / by Jang Hyun Han., 2013; Han, Jang Hyun (Box 92)
  - Seven / by Suck Zoo Han., 2013; Han, Suck Zoo (Box 92)
    Includes thesis and woodblock.
  - Doing things the hard way, taking things apart, and reinventing the wheel / by Tiffany Hockin., 2013; Hockin, Tiffany (Box 92)
  - Platform / by Eric Hu., 2013; Hu, Eric (Box 92)
  - Lost but seeking / by Azusa Kobayashi., 2013; Kobayashi, Azusa (Box 92)
  - Empty Orchestra / by Jen Lee., 2013; Lee, Kyong Won (Box 92)
  - Don't cover me / by Qiuye Liu., 2013; Liu, Qiuye (Box 89)
  - Manipulating the common / by Robert Matthews., 2013; Matthews, Robert (Box 92)
  - Undulations / by Cecilie Nellemann., 2013; Nellemann, Cecilie (Box 92)
  - One version of events or one possible view / by Julia Novitch., 2013; Novitch, Julia; 2 copies (Box 92)
  - Projection / by Jessica Svendsen., 2013; Svendsen, Jessica (Box 92)
  - [ces85] / by Chris Svensson., 2013; Svensson, Christopher Eric (Box 91)
    Includes a $1.00 USD bill.
  - 1156 Chapel Street / by Stefan Thorsteinsson., 2013; Thorsteinsson, Stefan (Box 92)
  - Spatial Repertoire / by Ghazaal Vojdani., 2013; Vojdani, Ghazaal (Box 92)
    Includes 4 parts and 1 postcard.
  - The sequence and its abolishment., 2014; Bitton, Nir (Box 93)
  - Abracadabra, 2014; Cho, Yu-Yeon (Box 93)
  - An a-b-c-d condition, 2014; Doria de Souza, João (Box 93)
  - The cartographer's mad project, 2014; Inbar, Shira Grace (Box 93)
  - Stay true, soft finish, superbalanced, 2014; Kitchen, Marina Mills (Box 93)
  - Common spaces, 2014; Konapelsky, Kellie Michelle (Box 93)
  - Constant calibration; never not testing, 2014; Kuhnke, Sean Ervan (Box 93)
  - Actions, occurences: a state of being, 2014; Langer, Scott (Box 93)
  - Adventures in hardscapes, 2014; Lee, Min Hee (Box 93)
  - 100 Days of wearing all red, yellow, or blue, 2014; Lewis, Esther (Box 93)
  - Anticipation, 2014; McGill, Martha Kang (Box 93)
  - MIT guide to lock picking steal this book theory of the derive Eva & Franco Mattes: Software takes command the wretched of the screen punctuation marks masters of adaptive rhetoric (agency within systems), 2014; Momtazian, Houman (Box 93)
  - Fantastic, 2014; Moreno-Valle Diez-Barroso, Gina (Box 93)
    5 viewing apparati (includes 3D glasses); book housed in black slipcase with Fantastic embossed on front.
  - Positivity & imagination, 2014; Niznik, Benjamin Barret (Box 93)
    2 items spiral bound, accompanied by 1 booklet.
  - Catalogue raisonne, 2014; Park, Sun Young (Box 93)
  - Theses book, 2014; Robinson-Leo, Grace (Box 93)
  - Catalogue raisonné, 2014; Waterman, Lacey Blaire (Box 93)
  - With restraint, 2014; Yendrys, Sean (Box 93)
  - Practice of My Life, 2015; Chung, SeungEun (Box 94)
  - We Live in All Times, 2015; DeJong, Marvin (Box 95)
  - THESIS, 2015; Espinosa, Richard (Box 94)
  - Catalogue Raisonné, 2015; Gorman, Jonathan (Box 94)
  - There Are Some Holes in My Thesis, 2015; Hadar, Yotam (Box 94)
  - H.A.R.I.B.O., 2015; Hung, Jenny (Box 94)
  - Read between the lines, 2015; Jiang, Yuanchen (Box 94)
  - Hyper, 2015; Kim, HyoungKee (Box 97)
  - Push Play, 2015; Kim, Jiyoni (Box 98)
  - D S N R, 2015; Knutson, Erin (Box 98)
  - Transplants, 2015; Marwanga, Loide (Box 94)
  - Displaced Gaze, 2015; Nelson, Ryan (Box 96)
  - After Effects, 2015; Nylund, Eric (Box 95)
  - move imagine remove reimagine, 2015; Povoleri, Michela (Box 94)
  - Jumpers are goalposts, 2015; Prah, Nejc (Box 95)
  - Fragment of a Map of the Universe, 2015; Ripper, Timothy (Box 98)
  - Oikos, 2015; Roberts, Ria (Box 94)
  - The Pen is Mightier or The Fractal Filigree of Delicate Distinctions, 2015; Wolforth, John-Paul (Box 94)
  - Rotten Apples, 2016; Bek, Martin (Box 104)
  - h, w, d, 2016; Billman, Megan (Box 101)
  - Like, Don't Like, 2016; Foxgrover, Laura (Box 101)
  - Sum Total, 2016; Godfrey, Dora (Box 101)
  - Egalgorhythm, 2016; Graver, Joshua (Box 101)
  - 5678, 2016; Harris, Jerome (Box 101)
  - Between and Beyond, 2016; Hou, Ying (Box 101)
  - Knowing me Knowing you, 2016; Hughes, Allyn (Box 101)
  - NOT NEGOTIABLE, 2016; Kang, Moonsik (Box 103)
  - Organized Disorder, 2016; Kosmerl, Biba (Box 101)
  - One Coloring the Other, 2016; Fehrman-Lee, Benjamin (Box 101)
  - Camera, 2016; Li, Qiong (Box 102)
  - V VV VVV, 2016; Pahlevan, Maziyar (Box 101)
  - LEFT RIGHT UP DOWN BACK FRONT BACKWARD FORWARD OUT IN CENTER MIRROR, 2016; Portis, Sasha (Box 101)
  - Modern Nostalgic Fantasies, 2016; Rennie, Raf (Box 101)
  - Game is not over, 2016; Sovetov, Anton (Box 101)
  - From One To An Other, 2016; Tomov, Rosen (Box 101)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 21)
  - Unidentified [Bodoni], undated (Box 59)
  - White, undated (Box 27)
  - Tract, 2017; Booker, Chase (Box 107)
  - Mind Over Weather, 2017; Seokhorn, Choi (Box 107)
  - 81.-1., 1.-81., 2017; Combs, Laura (Box 107)
  - Some Machines, 2017; Ermolova, O. (Box 107)
  - Day Book, 2017; Freer, Erik (Box 107)
    Also contains 1 gold feather along with book
  - Resistance, 2017; Galez, Martha (Box 107)
  - POV, 2017; Ganz, Ben (Box 107)
  - The pages turn triggering shapes to shift, 2017; Hoving, Jacob (Box 107)
  - Look Again, 2017; Mathias, Theodore (Box 107)
  - A System of Fracturing, 2017; Pervaiz, Asad (Box 107)
  - One Hundred Percent, 2017; Pinto, Ana (Box 107)
  - Here There Somewhere, 2017; Potter, Caroline (Box 107)
  - Posthuman Polymythology, 2017; Raina, Anastasiia (Box 107)
  - HERE, 2017; Rypkema, Christopher (Box 107)
  - Believing in system and operating the system, 2017; Vasilyeva, Polina (Box 107)
  - it's a toy for make believe, 2017; Virgili, Franziska (Box 107)
  - Designed Objects, 2017; Barnes, Jensen (Box 80)